>> Brian Holt: 现在你可以在这里看到，我没有使用过这个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now as you can see here,
I haven't been using that.
其实我每次跑都跑得很漂亮
I actually have it runs
prettier every time I run save.
我要教你怎么做
So I'm gonna show you how to do that.
所以在 VS 代码中，转至 " 扩展" ，
So inside of VS Code,
go to the Extensions,
这里就是这里我有一个叫普雷特的人
which is this one here, and
I have one called prettier.
我确定这上面是最上面的
Which I'm pretty sure
is this top one here.
对这个
Yep, this one.
是有很多下载的那一个
It's the one that has a lot of downloads.
超过 800 万，只需说安装 >> Brian Holt: 好的，
So over eight million and just say install
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
一旦你安装好了我就想让你去你的设置
once you have that installed,
then I want you to go to your Settings.
因此，您可以通过 " 代码首选项设置 " 或 " 命令逗号" 来执行此操作。
So you can either do that through Code
Preferences Settings or Command Comma.
然后你需要为我做两件事情
And then you need to turn
on two things for me.
您想打开的其中一个是 " 保存时的格式 " 。
One of them you wanna turn
on is Format on Save.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，在 " 保存 " 上使用编辑器格式，请检查该格式，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
the editor format on Save, check that one,
可能是给你的
that's probably off for you.
我希望您检查的第二个是配置。
The second one that I want you
to check is require config.
你可以看到我没查过我的
So prettier down here,
you can see, mine's not checked.
因此， prettier 需要配置。
So prettier, require config.
>> Brian Holt: 请检查该图。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So check that one.
所以你想让漂亮的人跑来
So you want prettier to run but
你只希望它能在最漂亮的项目上运行，对吗 ?
you only want it to run on projects that
prettier's actually installed on, right?
你不想再去别的项目有预作了
You don't wanna go on to some other
project and have prettier run on it
因为你要修改每一行代码然后
because then you're going to modify
literally every line of code and then
我要说的是你要把责任推到你身上
the get blame is gonna be on you for every
line of code which is unfun, I will say.
既然我这么做了这个项目还没有配置
So now that I've done that,
this project doesn't have a config yet,
我们还没做过
we haven't made one.
所以如果我去做这个，我就在保存它，注意它不固定它。
So if I go and do this, I'm saving it,
and notice that it's not fixing it.
这就是我们现在想要的对吗
That's what we want right now, right?
我们只希望它能在它有前地的项目上运行。
We only want it to run on
projects where it has prettier.
接下来我们要做的就是创建一个配置文件。
So the next thing we're going to do is
we're going to create a config file.
因此，创建新文件会将其保存到根
So create a new file save it to the root
我和你必须得
directory here adopt me and you have to
将此调用称为 dot.prettierRC。
call this call it dot.prettierRC.
>> Brian Holt: 我甚至不知道 RC 代表什么，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I don't even
know what RC stands for, but
调用所有 bash 配置文件。
that what all the bash
config files are called.
我们将创建一个名为 ES lint RC， prettier RC， MVM RC， MPM RC。
We're gonna create one called the ES
lint RC, prettier RC, MVM RC, MPM RC.
有人知道那代表什么吗
Does anyone know what that stands for?
我也不知道
Me neither.
好的， prettierRC 制作该文件。
Okay, prettierRC make that file.
是的我知道这是备用文件这是故意的
Yes I know it's a reserve file,
that's on purpose.
然后我需要你把两个神奇的角色放在这里，空的物体。
And then I need you to put two magical
characters in here, empty objects.
现在有几件事是你可以配置的
Now there are a few things you can
configure about prettier, you know,
如果您想成为选项卡或空间，您是否希望在此处使用空格，或者
if you want to be tabs or spaces,
do you wanted to have spaces here, or
没有空间吗
not have spaces there?
有几件事
There's a few things.
我告诉过你我不关心我只是想让它工作
I told you, I don't actually care,
I just want it to work.
所以这只是说，给我默认配置。
So this is just saying,
give me the default config.
但如果你想让它在这里有某种形式的配置
But if you want it to have
some sort of config in here,
你可以说 " singleQuote" : false。
you could say, "singleQuote": false.
我只想有双引号或单引号是真的
I only wanna have double quotes or
single quotes, true.
我只想用单引号对吗
I only wanna have single quotes, right?
会有那样的事但是我又不在乎
It'll be things like that,
but, again, I don't care,
所以我要把空的物体放在这里
so I'm just gonna put empty object here.
现在，如果我再返回两个 app.js ，我就省了，现在它会真正使用。
So now if I go back over two app.js and
I save, now it'll actually use.
它会在我每次保存的时候都跑出来，这是我想要的。
It'll run prettier on every single time
that I save which is what I wanted.
>> Brian Holt: 可以使用 sublime 来完成此操作。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This can
be done with sublime.
也可以使用其他编辑器来完成此操作。
This can be done with
other editors as well.
把它从 prettier的网站上读出来
Just read it off of prettier's website.
他们会告诉你怎么做
They'll tell you how to do it.
>> Brian Holt: 有关该问题的问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Questions about that?
这是为人民工作吗 ?
Is that working for people?
太酷了
Cool.
我还是喜欢这个因为它意味着我就像我大脑中的一部分
Again I love this because it means I get
to shut down like a part of my brain that
思考格式化事物。
thinks about formatting things.
就像你粘贴某样东西的时候
Like typically when you paste something
and it's like, okay well this has to go
我得把这些空间转换成选项卡之类的
here and I have to convert these
spaces to tabs and stuff like that.
你只需闭上你脑中的线就能把重点放在代码上
You just get to shut down that thread
of your brain and focus more on code.
如果您想有一个代码，那么对于 prettier ，不存在非常多的替代方法
There aren't really very many alternatives
for prettier so if you want to have a code
或者如果这是您想要的标准，那么您需要预先设置的格式。
format or if that's something that you
want prettier's by far the standard.
可能有其他的，但要么就是这个要么什么都没有。
There may be others but
it’s either this or nothing.
ESLint 有一个称为修订的东西，您也可以使用该修订。
ESLint has a thing called fix
which you can use that as well but
这也不是一回事
it’s not the same thing.